<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <packageId>AmCh.ImprovedNeedIndicator</packageId>
  <name>Improved Need Indicator</name>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.5.4069.20240501Z</modVersion>
  <authors>
    <li>AmCh</li>
    <li>Missionz3r0</li>
  </authors>
  <url>https://github.com/AmCh-Q/RimWorldMod_ImprovedNeedIndicator</url>
  <description>
A pawn has several needs. If you hover over those needs, you'll see a tooltip.
This tooltip has some helpful text, but it could be better.

Improved Need Indicator adds helpful timers to a need's tooltip so you know
exactly how long you have until that need is unfulfilled.

Implemented:
* Food
* Indoors
* Outdoors
* Recreation
* Rest

On Deck:
* Beauty

Upcoming:
* Chemical
* Comfort
* Deathrest
* Energy
* Kill Satiety
* Learning
* Play

Why?
  Because I spent three hours building a spreadsheet to figure out how long my pawns sleep and just knew there had to be a better way. Sleep alone is a complicated formula using the pawn's own 'Rest Rate Multiplier', bed type, bed material, bed quality, and number of sleep accelorators. Did you know making the bed out of marble to get that sweet beauty bonus makes your pawn sleep longer? Or that Jade doesn't count as stone and works the same as wood? Who knew?! I fricken didn't.

  Don't fall down the same rabbit hole I did. We've done the work for you here. Install the mod, shower us with praise, and sleep better than ever.

Who
  AmCh: Coding and Language Translations
  Missionz3r0: Coding and DevOps

  I (missionz3r0) want to convey my thanks to AmCh. They did the lions share of the coding in this mod. Be sure to shower them with adulations.

GitHub:
  https://github.com/AmCh-Q/RimWorldMod_ImprovedNeedIndicator

Some of our other mods:
  More Sleep Accelerators: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3201556917
  Need Bar Overflow: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2566316158
  </description>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/</downloadUrl>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
